Finding Aid for the Lesbian Love Records LSC.2207
UCLA Library Special Collections
Lesbian Love records
circa 1990
UCLA Library Special Collections
Love, B.
June L. Mazer Lesbian Archives
LSC.2207
1 Linear Feet (1 carton)
B. Love was a radio personality who hosted shows on the listener-sponsored radio station KPFK, based out of North Hollywood, California. The content of the programs was based on lesbian lives and ranged from issues of spirituality to call-in shows and interviews. This collection consists of 36 audio reels containing interviews, poetry, outtakes, and other audio recordings from her radio program "Lesbian Love."
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains processed audiovisual materials. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection is part of an outreach and collection-building partnership between the June L. Mazer Lesbian Archives, the UCLA Center for the Study of Women (CSW), and the UCLA Library.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
9973847753606533
We are committed to providing ethical, inclusive, and anti-racist description of the materials we steward, and to remediating existing description of our materials that contains language that may be offensive or cause harm. We invite you to submit feedback about how our collections are described, and how they could be described more accurately, by filling out the form located on our website: Report Potentially Offensive Description in Library Special Collections.
Sponsor
The June L. Mazer Lesbian Archive at UCLA is an outreach and collection-building partnership between the June L. Mazer Lesbian Archives, the UCLA Center for the Study of Women (CSW), and the UCLA Library. These collections expand the pool of primary source materials available to researchers and to the community at large. This partnership was initiated by CSW and is funded by the National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) to inventory, organize, preserve, and digitize more than eighty Mazer collections pertaining to lesbian and feminist activism and writings.
Biographical History
B. Love was a radio personality who hosted shows on the listener-sponsored radio station KPFK, based out of North Hollywood, California. The content was based on lesbian lives and ranged from issues of spirituality to call-in shows and interviews. Lesbian Love was one of these shows.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of 36 audio reels containing interviews, poetry, outtakes, and other audio recordings from the radio program Lesbian Love, broadcast on KPFK.
Radio programs for gays -- California -- Los Angeles.; Lesbian Love (Radio program) -- Archives.; KPFK (Radio Station: Los Angeles, Calif.); June L. Mazer Lesbian Archives
- Aleida Rodriguez, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_001; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:30:47) (Box 2, Case 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Transcribed from container: "Aleida Rodriguez (Alāda)" clarifying pronunciation; Transcribed from reel: "ALT END".
- Aleida Rodríguez 2, 2019 August 26; yrlsc_2207_002_002; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:15) (Box 2, Case 2)
  Transcribed from container: "2 Aleida Rodriguez"; Transcribed from reel: "AP / 10:32".
- Angel, 2019 December 18; yrlsc_2207_002_003; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:17:42) (Box 2, Case 3)
  Transcribed from container: "Angel for Leather and Lace Ethics"; Transcribed from reel: "2" and "AP 11:32"
- El Salva, 2019 September 9; yrlsc_2207_002_004; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:12:40) (Box 2, Case 4)
  Transcribed from reel: "AP 4:30" and "El Salva TARDY"
- Holly Near; Outtakes for Incest Survivors, 1985 July 7; yrlsc_2207_002_005; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:10:39) (Box 2, Case 5)
  Transcribed from reel: "Holly Near - 'Simply My Love for a Woman' 4 cuts B Love, Jennie H--, outtakes for Incest Survivors" and "Chrysler Magnum 7/24/85 30 ips".
- Jill McCellar (McCellan), yrlsc_2207_002_006; 1 Sound Recordings (Box 2, Case 6)
  Audiotape is blank.
- Jill McCellar (McCellan) 2, yrlsc_2207_002_007; 1 Sound Recordings (Box 2, Case 7)
- Kitty Tsui Poems, 2019 August 20; yrlsc_2207_002_008; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:04:42) (Box 2, Case 8)
  Transcribed from container: "THE JAZZ SHOW Wknd 12-24-88 HOUR #2 tails out" and "Kitty Tsui Poems! Strong". Transcrived from reel: "Phil S---".
- Kitty Tsui, Annetta + Auntie, 2019 August 20; yrlsc_2207_002_009; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:17:14) (Box 2, Case 9)
  Transcribed from container: "Kitty Tsui tails out Annetta + Auntie a poem in two voices."
- Lesbian Connectionist Spirituality, 1990 June 3; yrlsc_2207_002_010; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:07:21) (Box 2, Case 10)
  Transcribed from container: "6/90 Lesbian Connectionist Spirituality cuts edited fr. original tape"; see inserts in container for show notes
- Ravine, yrlsc_2207_002_011; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:18:45) (Box 2, Case 11)
  Transcribed from container: "18 mins Ravine edited uncensored no music Kali Angry Dyke Journal Aug '89 2 Mother poems Dreams Housewife Alcoholism"
- Ravine 2, yrlsc_2207_002_012; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:18:15) (Box 2, Case 12)
  Transcribed from container: "THE JAZZ SHOW Wknd 8-20-89 HOUR #2"; "Original Ravine Kinky as Hell [...]"; "edited [and] bleeped".
- Songhawk, tape 1 of 2, yrlsc_2207_002_013; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:05) (Box 2, Case 13)
  Transcribed from container: "7/90 tape 1 of 2 Songhawk".
- Songhawk, tape 2 of 2, yrlsc_2207_002_014; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:30:04) (Box 2, Case 14)
  Transcribed from container: "7/90 tape 2 of 2 Songhawk".
- Terry Wolverton, 2019 October 15; yrlsc_2207_002_015; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:04:26) (Box 2, Case 15)
  Transcribed from container: "DLB Terry Wolverton intro In a Different Light Anthology performance artist suckubous "ass" anniversary"
- Yolanda, B + Josy, tape 1 of 3, 1990 May 26; yrlsc_2207_002_016; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:02) (Box 2, Case 16)
  Transcribed from container: "Yolanda, B + Josy taped 5/26/90 tape 1 of 3"; Content note: group discussion on Lesbian Connectionist Spirituality
- Yolanda, B + Josy, tape 2 of 3, 1990 May 26; yrlsc_2207_002_017; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:58) (Box 2, Case 17)
  Transcribed from contrainer: "Yolanda, B + Josy taped 5/26/90 tape 2 of 3".
- Yolanda, B + Josy, tape 3 of 3, 1990 May 26; yrlsc_2207_002_018; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:24) (Box 2, Case 18)
  Transcribed from container: "Yolanda, B + Josy taped 5/26/90 tape 3 of 3".
- Reel 19, yrlsc_2207_002_019; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:07:08) (Box 2, Case 19)
- Lesbian Incest Survivors, 1, yrlsc_2207_002_020; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:05) (Box 2, Case 20)
  Transcribed from container: "Jennifer Dai 1"; "Lesbian Incest Survivors".
- Lesbian Incest Survivors, 2, yrlsc_2207_002_021; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:26:30) (Box 2, Case 21)
  Transcribed from container: "IMRU B Love"; "Jennifer 1"; "Lesbian Incest Suvivors".
- Lesbian Incest Survivors, 3, yrlsc_2207_002_022; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0;32:13) (Box 2, Case 22)
  Transcribed from container: "Lesbian Incest Survivors"; "2 Dai cont, Carol Beverage, Sandy Nelsun, Lisa Ann".
- Lesbian Incest Survivors, 4, yrlsc_2207_002_023; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:12) (Box 2, Case 23)
  Transcribed from container: "4 Carmon cont Jennie Balise"; "Lesbian Incest Survivors".
- Lesbian Incest Survivors, 5, yrlsc_2207_002_024; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:03) (Box 2, Case 24)
  Transcribed from container: "Lesbian Incest Survivors"; "3 Lisa Ann cont, Al - Alice, Vera, Kiko, Marti (Alpha), Destiny" [crossed out name] "Charlene, Carmon".
- Differently Abled Dykes, 1, yrlsc_2207_002_025; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:19:03) (Box 2, Case 25)
  Transcribed from container: "Cindy Forth deaf Outtakes Differently abled Dyke".
- Differently Abled Dykes, 2, 2019 September 9; yrlsc_2207_002_026; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration: 0:23:22) (Box 2, Case 26)
  Transcribed from container: "Debbie L-- + T-- Palmer Differently Abled Dykes Outtakes 2/2". The two names are possibly Debbie Laurence and Thesette Palmer.
- Degania Outtakes, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_027; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration: 0:12:13) (Box 2, Case 27)
  Transcribed from container: "Degonia OUT-TAKES"; "Old Lesbians Degonia Golove outtakes"
- Jean Bell Outtakes, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_028; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration: 0:17:40) (Box 2, Case 28)
  Transcribed from container: "Old Lesbians 3/90 Jean Bell Outtakes"; "Psychedelic Psnack Wk of 8-29-88"; "Blase Bonpane in Nic. monitoring the Nic elections."; "OUT-TAKES JEAN Bell 60+"
- Differently Abled Dykes, 3, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_029; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration: 0:21:53) (Box 2, Case 29)
  Transcribed from container: "Kay Cooley strike differently abled dykes Outtakes".
- Kitty Tsui Outtakes, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_030; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration 0:03:32) (Box 2, Case 30)
  Transcribed from container: "Kitty Tsui OUTTAKE"; "SSC1157"; "BUCKY/DENIAL"
- Differently Abled Dykes, 4, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_031; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration 0:24:59) (Box 2, Case 31)
  Transcribed from container: "Shaila Morgan - deaf differently abled Dykes Out Ta[kes]"
- Ravine Outtakes, yrlsc_2207_002_032; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration 0:11:45) (Box 2, Case 32)
  Transcribed from container: "Ravine Outtakes 7/90"
- Differently Abled Dykes, 5, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_033; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration: 0:18:06) (Box 2, Case 33)
  Transcribed from container: "Robbie McDaniels Lupus Differently Abled Dykes Outtakes"; "Save Our Beach GirlPin"
- Latina Lesbian Writers, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_034; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration: 0:29:01) (Box 2, Case 34)
  Transcribed from container: "Toni Garcia + Teri De la Penia Jenie Cordova Latina Lesbian Writers Outtakes"; "Toni Garcia Cordova Teri De La Penia Out take".
- Differently Abled Dykes, 6, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_035; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration: 0:34:37) (Box 2, Case 35)
  Transcribed from container: "Thesette Palmer and Debbie Laurence Differrently Abled Dykes Outakes 1-2"; "AP 12:32"
- Yolanda Ritter Outtakes, 2019; yrlsc_2207_002_036; 1 Sound Recordings (1/ 1/4 inch audiotape: Duration: 0:11:15) (Box 2, Case 36)
  Transcribed from container: "Youlanda Ritter Outtakes"; "NAVAJO". Transcribed from insert: "OUTTAKES OF YOLANDA RITTER"